Anita Weschler Papers
Anita Weschler Papers
- Writings
  - Writings of others
    - Fragment, unidentified (Box 83)
Solomon, Herbert E. [circa 1920] [Nov 20, 1921 PM] Jun 17, 1922 Jul 19, 1922 Aug 18, 1922 [circa 1922] Jul 29, 1923 Nov 24, 1923 [Jan 23, 1924 PM] Feb 1, 1924 Feb 3, 1924 [Feb 6, 1924 PM] Feb 20, 1924 Feb 26, 1924 Mar 3, 1924 [Mar 7, 1924 PM] [Mar 17, 1924 PM] [Apr 1, 1924 PM] [May 16, 1924 PM] [May 17, 1924 PM] [May 29, 1924 PM] [May 31, 1924 PM] Jun 8, 1924 [Jul 7, 1924 PM] [Jul 8, 1924 PM] [Jul 18, 1924 PM] [Sep 7, 1924 PM] [Sep 11, 1924 PM] [Sep 14, 1924 PM] [Sep 19, 1924 PM] [Sep 21, 1924 PM] [Sep 26, 1924 PM] [Oct 5, 1924 PM] Oct 14 [1924 PM] [Oct 21, 1924 PM] [Oct 25, 1924 PM] [Dec 1, 1924 PM] [Dec 7, 1925 PM] [Jan 3, 1926 PM] [Jan 4, 1926 PM] Jan 5, 1926 [Jan 6, 1926 PM] [Jan 9, 1926 PM] [Jan 10, 1926 PM] [Jan 12, 1926 PM] [Jan 13, 1926 PM] [Jan 14 1926 PM] Jan 19 [circa 1926] Jan 19 [circa 1926] Jan 21 [circa 1926] [Jan 21, 1926 PM] Jan 23 [circa 1926] Jan 26, 1926 Jan 27, 1926 Jan 28, 1926 Jan 28, 1926 [Jan ? 1926 PM] Jul 13 [circa 1926] Aug 4 [circa 1926] [Aug 5, 1926 PM] [Aug 7, 1926 PM] [Aug 8, 1926 PM] [Aug 10, 1926 PM] [Aug 11, 1926 PM] [Aug 13, 1926 PM] [Aug 15, 1926 PM] Sep 22, 1926 Oct 8, 1926 [circa 1926] [circa 1926] [circa 1926] [circa 1926] Jul 14, 1927 Jul 16, 1927 Jul 18, 1927 Jul 22, 1927 Jul 23 [1927 PM] Jul 23 [1927 PM] Jul 28, 1927 Jul 28, 1927 Jul 31 [1927 PM] Aug 1, 1927 Aug 2 [1927 PM] Aug 5 [1927 PM] Aug 7 [1927 PM] Aug 14 [1927 PM] Aug 15, 1927 Aug 16, 1927 Aug 27, 1927 Aug 30, 1927 Mar 30 [1928 PM] [Apr 6, 1928 PM] Apr 13 [1928 PM] Apr 29 [1928 PM] May 1, 1928 [May 6, 1928] [May 8, 1928 PM] [May 12, 1928 PM] [May 13, 1928 PM] [May 15, 1928 PM] [May 18, 1928 PM] [May 22, 1928 PM] [May 24, 1928 PM] [May 26, 1928 PM] [May 26, 1928 PM] [Jun 2, 1928 PM] [Jun 24, 1928 PM] [Jun 26, 1928 PM] [Jun 29, 1928 PM] Jul 1, 1928 [Jul 10, 1928 PM] [Jul 13, 1928 PM] [Jul 16, 1928 PM] [Aug 9, 1928 PM] [Aug 12, 1928 PM] [Aug 17, 1928 PM] [Aug 19, 1928 PM] [Sep 7, 1928 PM] [Sep 10, 1928 PM] [Sep 13, 1928 PM] [Sep 17, 1928 PM] [Dec 12, 1928 PM] [circa Dec ? 1928] [circa 1928] Jul 25 [circa 1929] [Jul 26, 1929 PM] [Jul 30, 1929 PM] [Jul 30, 1929 PM] Aug 1 [1929 PM] [Aug 5, 1929 PM] [Aug 9, 1929 PM] [circa 1929] [Jan 4, 1930 PM] [Jan 9, 1930 PM] [Mar 14, 1930 PM] [Jun 2, 1930 PM] [Nov 8, 1930 PM] Nov 30 [circa 1930] [circa 1930] [circa 1930] [circa 1930] [circa 1930] [circa 1930] [circa 1930] [circa 1930] [circa 1930] [Mar 24, 1931 PM] [Mar 27, 1931 PM] [Aug 6, 1931 PM] [Aug 12, 1931 PM] [Oct 23 PM] [circa 1931] Nov 2, 1931 [Nov 3, 1931 PM] [Nov 3, 1931 PM] Nov 15, 1931 [circa 1931] [circa 1931] [circa 1931] [circa 1931] [circa 1931] [circa 1931] [Jan 2, 1932 PM] [Jan 17, 1932 PM] [Jan 27, 1932 PM] [Jan 29, 1932 PM] [Feb 4, 1932 PM] Apr 18, 1932 [Apr 21, 1932 PM] [Apr 26, 1932 PM] [May 12, 1932 PM] [May 30, 1932 PM] [May 31, 1932 PM] [Jul 13, 1932 PM] [Jul 18, 1932 PM] [Jul 20, 1932 PM] Aug 4, 1932 Aug 8 [1932 PM] Aug 26 [1932 PM] [Nov 23, 1932 PM] [Dec 2, 1932 PM] [Dec 24, 1932 PM] [circa 1932] [circa 1932] [circa 1932] [Jun 6, 1934 PM] [Jun 6, 1934 PM] [Jun 18, 1934 PM] Jun 18 [1934 PM] [Jul 26, 1934 PM] [Jul 4, 1935 PM] [Sep 2, 1935 PM] [circa 1935] [Jun 9, 1936 PM] [Jun 9, 1936 PM] [Jun 24, 1936 PM] [Jun 27, 1936 PM] [Jun 29, 1936 PM] [Jul 2, 1936 PM] [Jul 7, 1936 PM] [Jul 14, 1936 PM] Jul 22 [circa 1936] [Aug 11, 1936 PM] [Aug 24, 1936 PM] Aug 14, 1937 Jul 17, 1939 [Jul 25, 1939 PM] [Jul 26, 1939 PM] [Jul 28, 1939 PM] [circa 1939] Jul 28 [1940 PM] Aug 9 [1940 PM] Aug 14, 1940 Dec 30 [1940 PM] Apr 15 [circa 1941] Jun 10 [1941 PM] Jun 13 [1941 PM] Jun 24 [1941 PM] Jul 1 [1941 PM] Jul 14 [1941 PM] *Jul 29 [circa 1941] *Aug 22 [1941 PM] [circa 1941] *Dec 18, 1942 [1943] *Feb 1, 1944 *Feb 2, 1944 *Mar 1, 1944 Mar 15, 1944 Mar 31, 1944 [Feb 4, 1948 PM] Jan 3, 1949 [Jan 28, 1949 PM] [Jan 31, 1949 PM] [Feb 4, 1949 PM] [Feb 10, 1949 PM] [Feb 14, 1949 PM] [Feb 18, 1949 PM] [Feb 21, 1949 PM] [Feb 28, 1949 PM] [Mar 5 PM] [circa 1949] [Mar 8, 1949 PM] [Jan 21, 1950 PM] [Jan 25, 1950 PM] [Mar 31, 1950 PM] *Apr 6, 1950 [Apr 7, 1950 PM] Apr 11, 1950 [Apr 11, 1950 PM] [Apr 18, 1950 PM] [Apr 20, 1950 PM] [Apr 20, 1950 PM] [Apr 21, 1950 PM] [Apr 28, 1950 PM] [May 3, 1950 PM] [May 9, 1950 PM] [May 16, 1950 PM] May 25 [1950 PM] [1950] [1950] Feb 4, 1951 *Mar 9, 1951 [Mar 11, 1951 PM] [Sep 12, 1951 PM] [Sep 12, 1951 PM] [Sep 13, 1951 PM] [Sep 25, 1951 PM] [Sep 28, 1951 PM] [1951 PM] Oct 4 [1951 PM] *Oct 6, 1951 *Oct 10, 1951 Oct 10, 1951 [Oct 15, 1951 PM] *Oct [?]1951 [1951 PM] [1951 PM] [circa 1951] *Dec 23, 1953 [Apr 3, 1955 PM] *Jul 31, 1955 *[Jul 1955] *Aug 1, 1955 Aug 3 [1955 PM] *Aug 5, 1955 Aug 28 [1955 PM] Jul 10 [1956 PM] Jul 16 [1956 PM] [Jul 24, 1956 PM] [Aug 6, 1956 PM] [Aug 13, 1956 PM] *Aug 16, 1956 [Aug 21, 1956 PM] *Aug 27 [1956 PM] *Jul 28, 1958 *Apr 6, 1959 [Jun 2, 1959 PM] *Oct 6, 1959 *Sep 18 [1959 PM] *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d.
Solomon, Mitzi (1918- ) Aug 22, 1944 *Aug 23, 1944 [Feb 22, 1946 PM] [Apr 29, 1947 PM]
Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum Nov 5, 1954 Apr 12, 1956 n.d.
Sommerich, Jane Sep 4, 1942 [Jul 22, 1943 PM] Apr 3, 1944 Oct 18, 1944 Nov 3, 1944 Dec 11, 1944 Jan 7, 1945 [May 26, 1945 PM] Feb 11, 1946 [Oct 13, 1946 PM] Mar 1, 1948 Nov 29, 1948 [1948] Jan 5, 1949 Jan 8, 1949 Mar 12, 1949 [Dec 1949] Jan 15, 1950 Feb 7, 1950 Mar 13, 1950 Apr 28, 1950 [Apr 1950] [Dec 14, 1950 Pm] Apr 19, 1951 Mar 16, 1952 n.d.
Spenser, James Houston [circa Jul 1934 Aug 2, 1934 Aug 14, 1934 [Aug 21, 1934 PM] Sep 2, 1934 Sep 22, 1934 Sep 27, 1934 Oct 17, 1934 Nov 5, 1934 Nov 10, 1934 Dec 27, 1934 Jan 16, 1935 [Jan 30, 1935 PM] Feb 1, 1935 Feb 16, 1935 Mar 2, 1935 Apr 3, 1935 Apr 20, 1935 Aug 20, 1935 Aug 30, 1935 Dec 11, 1935 [Dec 17, 1935 PM] Feb 10, 1936 [Feb 12, 1936 PM] Sep 5, 1936 Oct 31, 1936 Mar 3, 1937 Apr 14, 1937 May 4, 1937 Mar 9, 1938 Jan 16, 1939 Aug 14, 1939 Dec 13, 1939 Jan 22, 1940 Feb 8, 1941 Apr 3, 1941 Apr 25, 1941 Nov 15, 1941 [Jun 9, 1942 PM] Nov 8, 1944 Mar 30, 1955 n.d.
S. S. Stafford, Inc. Aug 23, 1957 [Sep 1957] *Oct 16, 1957
Staloff, Edward Feb 9 [1937]
Stern, Edgar Jul 9 [1934 PM] Jul 18 [1934 PM]
Stringham, Edwin J. [Feb 1937]
Suffolk Museum at Stony Brook, Long Island Aug 14, 1947
Sunshine, Ethel [Jul 12, 1954 PM] [Aug 19, 1954 PM] [circa 1954]
Taussig, Mary C. Sep 3, 1930
Telfair Academy of Arts and Sciences Oct 5, 1953 Oct 5, 1953 *Oct 6, 1953 *[circa Oct 1953] *Dec 12, 1954 Jan 14, 1954 Jan 18, 1954 *Jan 24, 1954 Feb 1, 1954 Jul 7, 1955 n.d. n.d.
Thompson, Sydney [Feb 1937
Toledo Museum of Art May 28, 1953
Towsend Publication Jun 12, 1931
Torrence, Ridgely Feb 22, 1937
Ulreich, Bukannura (1899-1950) [Sep 15, 1928 PM] [Oct 8, 1928 PM] Apr 21, 1929 Jul 31, 1329 [circa 1929] [circa 1929] [Mar 15, 1931] [Mar 27, 1931 PM] [Apr 19, 1932 PM] [Apr 22, 1932 PM] [Jan 6, 1933] Jun 7, 1934 Jun 14, 1934 [Aug 7, 1935 PM] [Oct 31, 1936 PM] [Jun 29, 1938 PM] [Mar 8, 1945 PM] [circa 1945] [Nov 26, 1948 PM] [Sep 1, 1949 PM] n.d. n.d. n.d.
Usigli, Rudolfo Mar 29, 1953 May 26, 1953 Sep 16, 1953 Jul 15, 1955
U.S. Treasury Department Apr 21, 1936
Valentin, Curt Oct 15, 1943 Apr 20, 1953
Vitarelli, V. Dec 27, 1949 *[circa Jan 1950] Jan 26, 1956 Jul 16, 1956 Jul 31, 1956 *Aug 4, 1956 Aug 6, 1956 Aug 10, 1956 Aug 13, 1956 Aug 20, 1956 Oct 3, 1956
Walton, Eda Lou Jan 30, 1937
Warnecke, Heinz (1895- ) Dec 11, 1950
Wasey, Jane Dec 7, 1950 Mar 16, 1951 [May 4, 1951 PM]
Watson, Forbes *Feb 15, 1939
Wellons Gallery, Ltd. May 22, 1956 *May 23, 1956 Sep 14, 1956 Oct 2, 1956 Oct 4, 1956 Oct 17, 1956 Jan, 1957 [circa 1957]
Weschler, Adolphus Dec 11, 190[3] Apr 24 [1924 PM] Mar 8, 1932 Nov 21, 1932 Dec 6, 1932 Nov 23, 1933 Apr 8, 1935 [Jun 4, 1937 PM] Jun 12, 1939 Jun 14, 1939 Jun 27, 1939 [Jul 15, 1939] [Jul 22, 1939] Jul 23, 1939 Oct 15, 1939 Dec 13, 1939 Feb 19, 1940 Mar 7, 1940 Mar 13, 1940 Apr 15, 1940 Apr 18, 1940 Apr 26, 1940 [Sep 16, 1940 PM] Nov 17, 1940 [Apr 13, 1941 PM] Jun 12 [1941 PM] Oct 10 [1941 PM] Apr 25 [1942 PM] May 2 [1942 PM] Oct 13, 1945 Dec 16, 1945 Sep 1, 1952 [Nov 7, 1952 PM] May 8, 1956 May 14, 1956 May 28, 1956 Dec 27, 1956 Mar 31, 1959 Apr 15, 1959 n.d.
Weschler, Hulda Mayer [circa 192?] *May 30, 1922 Jun 2, 1922 Jun 8, 1922 Jun 9, 1922 Jul 16, 19[22] Sep 28, 1922 [Jun 19, 1923 PM] Jul 2, 1923 Jul 5, 1923 [Jul 16, 1923 PM] Jul 23, 1923 [Jul 31, 1923 PM] [Aug 1, 1923 PM] [1923 PM] [1923 PM] [1923 PM] Jun 2, 1924 Jun 2 [circa 1924] Jun 5, 1924 [Jun 10, 1924 PM] Jun 23 [1924 PM] [Jul 9, 1924 PM] Jul 14, 1924 Jul 20, 1924 Jul 29 [1924] [Aug 7, 1924 PM] [Aug 8, 1924 PM] [Aug 16, 1924 PM] [Aug 20, 1924 PM] [circa 1924] [circa 1924] [circa 1924] [Jul 8, 1925 PM] [Jul 17, 1925 PM] Jul 21 [1925 PM] Jul 22 [circa 1925] Jul 28 [1925 PM] Aug 6 [1925 PM] Aug 17, 1925 [circa 1925] [circa 1925] Jul 10 [1926 PM] May 1, 1928 [May 1928 PM] Jun 17 [1928 PM] Jun 18 [1928 PM] Jun 19, 1928 Jul 1 [1928 PM] Aug 29 [circa 1928] Sep 3, 1928 [Sep 14, 1928 PM] [Sep 20, 1928 PM] [Nov 13, 1928 PM] [circa 1928] [circa 1928] [circa 1928] [circa 1928] [circa 1928] [circa 1928] Aug 2 [1929 PM] *Nov 11, 1929 *Jul 27, [192?] *Jan 14 [1930 PM] *Aug 17 [circa 1930] [circa 1930] [circa 1930] [Feb 13, 1931 PM] [Mar 20, 1931 PM] Mar 27, 1931 [Jun 28, 1931 PM] Jul 31, 1931 Aug 22 [circa 1942] Jul 13 [1948]
Weschler, J. Charles ( - 1959) *Jun 13, 1922 Jul 16, 1923 [Jul 22, 1923 PM] [Jul 23, 1923 PM] Jul 31, 1923 Jun 27 [1924 PM] Jul 19 [1924] [Aug 4, 1924 PM] Aug 7, 1924 Aug 15, 1925 May 2, 1928 [May 16, 1928 PM] [May 21, 1928 PM] [Jun 22, 1928 PM] [Jun 25, 1928 PM] [Jul 14, 1928 PM] [Jul 17, 1928 PM] [Sep 11, 1928 PM] [Sep 14, 1928 PM] [Sep 14, 1928 PM] [circa 1928] [circa 1928] [circa 1928] [Jan 3, 1930 PM] Nov 15 [1930 PM] [circa 1930] [Feb 5, 1931 PM] [Jun 3, 1932 PM] [Jul 11, 1932 PM] Jul 18 [1932 PM] [Jul 20, 1932 PM] [Aug 25, 1932 PM] [Jul 25, 1932 PM] [circa 1932] [Jun 12, 1934 PM] [Jun 15, 1934 PM] [Jun 26, 1934 PM] [Jun 30, 1934 PM] [Jul 13, 1934 PM] [Jul 23, 1934 PM] Aug 22 [1934 PM] Jul 12 [circa 1925] Jul 31 [1935 PM] [Aug 20, 1935 PM] [Aug 24, 1935 PM] [Sep 6, 1935 PM] [Sep 16, 1935 PM] [circa 1935] [circa 1935] [Jun 19, 1936 PM] Jun 27, 1936 Jul 6, 1936 Jul 11, 1936 [Jul 17, 1936 PM] [Jul 24, 1936 PM] [Aug 5, 1936 PM] [Aug 19, 1936 PM] [Aug 27, 1936 PM] Jul 31, 1937 Jul 31, 1937 Aug 4, 1937 Aug 13, 1937 Aug 18, 1937 Aug 20, 1937 Aug 23, 1937 [Aug 26, 1937 PM] Sep 9, 1937 Sep 25, 1937 Aug 10, 1938 [Aug 10, 1938 PM] [Jul 26, 1940 PM] [Aug 8, 1940 PM] Jun 26 [1941 PM] [Jul 12, 1941 PM] [Jul 24, 1941 PM] Aug 12, 1941 PM [Aug 18, 194 PM] Aug 20, 1941 [Aug 13, 1945 PM] [Aug 13, 1945 PM] [Aug 20, 1945 PM] [Dec 28, 1945 PM] [1945?] [Aug 30, 1946 PM] [Aug 25, 1947 PM] [Aug 30, 1947 PM] [Sep 3, 1347 PM] [circa 194 [circa 1947] Jun 25 [1948 PM] Jun 30 [1948 PM] Jul 6 [1948 PM] Jul 8 [circa 1948] Jul 15 [circa 1948] [circa Jul 1948 [1948 PM] [Mar 8, 1949 PM] Apr 8, 1949 [Jan 8, 1950 PM] [1950 PM] [Aug 5, 1951 PM] [Jul 14, 1952 PM] Aug 18, 1952 Sep 19, 1952 Dec 23 [1952 PM] Jul 5 [circa 1953] [Jun 17, 1956 PM] [Aug 19, 1956 PM] [Aug 30, 1956 PM] [Jul 25, 1957 PM] Aug 27, 1957 Aug 29, 1957 *Sep 1, 1957 *Nov 12, 1957 *Nov 13, 1957 *Nov 14, 1957 *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d. *n.d.
Wescott, Glenway (1901- ) Jun 1, 1943 Nov 2, 1944 [Dec 31, 1945 PM] Nov 8, 1946 Dec 30, 1947
Wescott, Paul (1904- ) [Sep 12, 1929 PM Jul 31 [1930 PM] [Dec 18, 1930 PM] Dec 19 [1930 PM] [circa 1930] [1930 PM] [Jan 16, 1931 PM] [Feb 3, 1931 PM] *Oct 5, 1933
Weyhe Gallery Dec 26, 1951 Feb 8, 1952
Wheelock, Ralph A. Apr 30, 1948
Whiting, Frederic Allen (1873- ) Aug 11, 1938 *Sep 8, 1938 *Sep 19, 1938 Oct 28, 1938 *Nov 2, 1938 Nov 4, 1938 *Nov 5, 1938 *Nov 14, 1938 *Nov 14, 1938 *Nov 22, 1938 Nov 29, 1938 *Dec 1, 1938 Dec 5, 1938 *Dec 8, 1938 *Dec 12, 1938 *Dec 15, 1938 *Dec 16, 1938 *Dec 16, 1938 *Jan 6, 1939 *Aug 17, 1939
Whitney Museum of American Art Nov 16, 1934 Nov 12, 1935 Nov 12, 1935 Dec 11, 1935 Oct 1, 1937 *Jul 14, 1940 Oct 12, 1940 [Dec 28, 1940 PM] Mar 11, 1941 Feb 13, 1942 Feb 20, 1942 Feb 24, 1942 Feb 25, 1942 May 11, 1943 May 1 1, 1943 Oct 14, 1943 *Jun 8, 1944 Jun 28, 1944 Jan 9, 1946 *Jan 5, 1947 [Feb 22, 1947 PM] [Feb 26, 1947] [Jan 1948] [Mar 17, 1949 PM] *Oct 17, 1949 Feb 23, 1950 Mar 22, 1950 Jan 9, 1951 Feb 5, 1951 *Feb 10, 1951 May 3, 1951 Jun 26, 1951 Feb 7, 1952 Feb 29, 1952 Mar 4, 1952 Mar 4, 1952 [Apr 30, 1952 PM] Aug 5, 1952 Nov 7, 1952 Mar 30, 1953 May 26, 1953 Dec 29, 1954 Feb 16, 1955 Apr 4, 1956 [Jun 6, 1956 PM] [Oct 9, 1956 PM] [Oct 12, 1956 PM] Jan 24, 1957
Whitney, Parkhurst [Sep 30, 1935 PM] [Oct 4, 1935 PM] [Oct 8, 1935 PM] [Oct 17, 1935 PM] Oct 24, 1935 [Oct 28, 1935 PM] [Oct 30, 1935 PM] Nov 11, 1935 [Nov 14, 1935 PM] [Nov 18, 1935 PM] [Nov 20, 1935 PM] Nov 25, 1935 PM] [Nov 27, 1935 PM] [Dec 3, 1935 PM] [Dec 10, 1935 PM] [Dec 24, 1935 PM] [circa 1935] [Jan 8, 1936 PM] [Jan 20, 1936 PM] [Feb 21, 1936 PM] [Feb 21, 1936 PM] [Apr 30, 1936 PM] Aug 6, 1936 Aug 15, 1936 Aug 30, [1936 PM] [Nov 4, 1936 PM] [circa 1936] [circa 1936] [circa 1936] [Mar 9, 1937 PM] Dec 29, 1928 Jan 31, 1939 [Feb 23, 1939] Jul 31, 1939 Oct 3, 1939 Jan 1 [1940 PM] Jun 12, 1941 Jun 23, 1941 Jul 10, 1941 Aug 20, 1941 [Aug 29, 1941 PM] Nov 13, 1941 Feb 29, 1944 Apr 3, 1944 May 16, 1944 Jul 5, 1944 Jul 28, 1944 Aug 21, 1944 Nov 18, 1944 Jan 24, 1945 Feb 5, 1945 Mar 1 1, 1945 Apr 10, 1945 Nov 13, 1946 Nov 25, 1946 Jan 19, 1947 Mar 25, 1947 Sep 28, 1947 Dec 22, 1947 Feb 6, 1948 Mar 4, 1948 Dec 12, 1948 n.d. n.d. n.d.
Widdemer, Margaret (1895- ) Feb 8, 1937
Wilder, Thornton (1897- ) Feb 14, 1937 *Feb 16, 1937
Willets, Eliza L. [1936] Feb 9, 1937 Jun 3, 1938 Aug 19, 1938 [Oct 10, 1938 PM] Sep 3, 1939 Dec 29, 1939 Mar 22, 1945 Jan 7, 1946 Feb 4, 1946 Feb 7, 1946 Nov 29, 1946
Wilson, Helen Sep 15, 1951 [Sep ? 1958]
Wilson, Irene H. [Feb 1937]
Winegar, Anna Feb 11, 1937
Woman's Peace Union Apr 21, 1937
Wor De Klee, Inc. Nov 6, 1952 n.d.
Worcester Art Museum Dec 17, 1951
Yaddo Feb 17, 1956 Feb 29, 1956 *[Feb ? 1956] *Mar 13 [circa 1956] Jun 20, 1956
Zigrosser, Carl (1891- ) Oct 16, 1940
Zorach, Marguerite Thompson (1887- ) [Sep 24, 1937 PM] [Jul 23, 1940 PM] Jan 2 [1941 PM] [Jul 28, 1941 PM] [Jul 30, 1941 PM] [Jun 25, 1950 PM] Apr 1, 1951 Jun 30, 1951 [Jun 22, 1951 PM] Aug 15, 1954 [Sep 14, 1957 PM] [Oct 30, 1957 PM] [Sep 28, 1959 PM]
Zorach, William (1887-1967) Jun 3, 1931 Jun 5, 1931 [Aug 6 1931 PM] Jul 5 [1933 PM] Sep 25, 1933 Jul 28, 1934 [circa 1934] Sep 18, 1935 Jul 30, 1936 Dec 7, 1938 [Dec 17, 1938 PM] Jul 16, 1940 Jun 10, 1941 Aug 2, 1942 Jun 23, 1943 [Aug 2, 1943 PM] Jun 23, 1943 [Aug 2, 1943 PM] [1943] Jun 21, 1945 Sep 10, 1945 [Aug 3, 1946 PM] Sep 28, 1947 Dec 1, 1948 Feb 2, 1949 Dec 3 [1949 PM] [Apr 5, 1950 PM] Nov 13, 1951 Aug 1, 1952 [Oct 20, 1956 PM] Jan 10, 1958 [May 2, 1959 PM] n.d. n.d.